That I was so busy
in the hustle and bustle of other life that I could
not get time to sit and think
why I am doing what I am doing
and when I get this year, I think what I could
not understand
242 my son understood very quickly
and he knows everything there, even knowing
that talking to people about their death is
not an easy task, still he goes out
everyday to
make people responsible,
some people try very hard and cannot be met, if you
call them, they cut the call or pretend to be their
own, hello IG, I am
not interested, how many times have I heard that if we
look at it, why should any person talk about his death, the
subject itself is such
that people pretend to be ignorant even after knowing it,
I was thinking, is
your job here to force people to think, to
understand their needs and to give
them the right alternative according to their needs, some
people even avoid it by saying that you know
brother, you are only concerned about your commission
and nothing else, but he takes this also while laughing
You know why he's
a
loot because by seeing the right advice at the right time
he's helped so many families
and when he drinks the
peace of mind on the faces of the family members
that the world gets happiness that no commission
can give
[music]
I'm proud of my son because he's
helping people to be responsible towards their families that's not
even difficult but this storage
digestive right
that millions of people in the country are responsible